Hey, guys!
I think I see an island!
Hmm...
Looks uninhabited to me.
Ready the anchor!
Let's go check it out!
Find me some ingredients and
I'll start cooking lunch.
All right!
Listen, nothing's slimy or gross, okay?
What does it matter?
Once it's in your stomach,
it's all the same.
Get over yourself. Ow!
Hey, Chopper, did you
find any new herbs to use?
Mm-hmm.
This place has all sorts of neat stuff.
I got a good stock, but I'm still
looking in case I missed something.
Which reminds me, I noticed
something weird a second ago.
There's a little groove
along the trail here.
I wonder what it is.
Oh, you're right.
That is weird.
Looks like a bicycle or
something came through here.
Come on, that doesn't make any sense.
There's nobody else on the island.
Why would there be a bicycle?
Yeah, that's a good point.
Hey, check it out!
We're almost through the jungle!
Well, that's a letdown.
Just looks like a whole
lot of nothing out here.
He's excited.
Did I miss something?
I don't get it either.
Maybe he found some new herbs.
Huh?
Chopper, you cheater!
You were gonna hog that big mushroom
all to yourself, weren't you?
Get back here!
Hey, what happened? Are you OK?
There must be something behind that rock.
Come on, hurry.
Whoa, you're not a mushroom.
Hmm?
A raccoon dog.
Can't you see the antlers?
I'm a reindeer.
I saw you fall. Are you hurt?
Who the heck is that?
What's going on?
I don't know. Someone's here.
Do you mind?
I was sleeping.
Did you hit my friend?
Oh, man.
That guy is huge.
I thought we were alone on this island.
You know him?
Hey, is this guy an enemy?
Who is he?
If Robin's freaking out, then
so am I. Something's wrong.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on.
Look, I know you're surprised to
see me, but don't get so worked up.
It's not like I came here on
official orders or anything.
It's a nice day, so I decided
to go for a ride. Orders, huh?
And who is it you work for?
My, my.
You've grown into quite the
lovely lady, haven't you?
Nico Robin.
If you want to die, I will
protect you from the moment
Okay, let's go ahead and go ahead
The moon will always come to the moon
The wind will come to the sky
and see the light of the sky
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh.
This guy has Robin scared out
of her freaking mind. Why?
He's a Marine.
Navy Headquarters Admiral Aokiji.
Admiral?
Wait, you mean this guy's an admiral?
That's one of the highest ranks there is.
That's right.
There are only three
officers in the entire
Navy who currently hold
the position of admiral.
Akainu, Aokiji, and Kizaru.
The only one who outbreaks them is Fleet
Admiral Sengoku, the Navy's top official.
The man you see standing
before you is one of the three
men known as the world
government's ultimate powerhouses.
But why in the heck is
someone like this even here?
Should you be out hunting
some big-time pirates
with a bazillion berry
bounties or something?
Go away.
Huh?
Oh, my, my.
Another very sexy lady with super
big bazongas. Are you free tonight?
You watch your mouth, you lanky
jerk! Hey, focus! Pay attention!
Whoa, whoa, hold on a second, you guys.
Didn't you hear what I just said?
I'm just out taking a little stroll.
Don't get so worked up, okay?
I mean, you guys are just, you're like
just whatchamacallits, you know? What?
I forgot. Oh, well.
You're not making any sense, you weirdo!
Robin, are you kidding?
You must be mistaken him for someone else.
This doofus wouldn't pass for a
regular Marine, let alone an Admiral.
Hey, come on.
You shouldn't go around judging
people based on their appearance.
The motto I've always lived by as a
Marine is total, slovenly justice.
Then our judgment was right!
Anyway, what I was saying...
Excuse me a moment.
Being on my feet too long
makes me tired. Yeah?
Then maybe you shouldn't have been
sleeping standing up, you think?
What I was saying is
that I have no intention
of capturing you or anything like that,
so just take it easy.
I'm only here to confirm the
whereabouts of Nico Robin,
who hadn't been seen since
the Alabasta incident.
As we suspected, she's been with you.
That is one tall piece of apathy.
The only thing high-ranking
about him is his nerve.
I'll put some sort of report
together for headquarters later.
Now that you've added another crew
member who's got a price on her head,
your overall bounty has gone up.
$100 million plus $60 million
plus $79 million equals...
Ah, screw it.
Some big-ass number.
Just do the damn math.
That's it! Come, come!
Hold on, Yippie! Stop it!
What are you guys doing? Let me go!
Why are you trying to start
a fight with this guy?
Are you crazy?
He's one of the strongest
Marines there is!
I'm not just gonna stand around while this
jerk tries to take Robin away from us!
Take it easy.
I told you I'm not gonna
do anything, remember?
I told you I'm just
out on a stroll stroll
huh go take your stroll somewhere else
get out of here why are you so angry at
me looks like he's trying to pick a fight
so you're really a
marine I wish we'd known
that a lot sooner hey
who are all these people
Whoa, are you guys okay?
I thought this island was uninhabited.
Well, they're probably castaways
that washed up on the shore here.
There was a passenger liner that was
reported missing about a month ago.
Last seen somewhere in this area.
I'm guessing it sank.
And these are the survivors.
Okay, whatever.
I'll leave, but before I do.
You guys should gather your stuff
and get ready to leave, too.
Fortunately, I know of an inhabited island
that's not too far away from this one.
You should go there and
ask them to help you out.
Hey, you guys!
Don't believe a word he says!
Understand me?
This jerk's a marine officer!
So what? Is that a problem?
Oh, that's right. I get it.
I guess that makes sense.
Normally, the Marines are your friends
and the Pirates are the bad guys, right?
Stop it! What's so funny? Him?
How is he going to help
anybody? I don't know.
Heck, I don't even think he has a ship.
Other than ours, there isn't
another ship around anywhere.
Let's see.
There's no ship and nobody here
seems to have a Log Pose either.
How in the world are they supposed
to get to that island anyway?
Oh, they'll be fine.
Nothing you say sounds
the least bit convincing.
It's true.
He does have the power to help them.
That should do it!
We loaded them up with food and water.
It should be enough to last
them for quite a while.
Feels good to do a little
work from time to time.
Yeah, no doubt about that!
Hey, you know something?
You're not so bad.
What do you know?
They're hitting it off.
Okay, so now what?
Are you going to swim
to that island to drag
these guys and all their stuff behind you?
Don't be ridiculous.
All right, everybody, stay back.
What is that thing?
It's some kind of monster!
I bet it's the guardian
of this part of the sea!
Hey, you!
Run for it! Look out!
Get out of there!
Ice Age.
A Devil Fruit.
The sea, it's frozen.
This is the power of a
Navy Headquarters Admiral.
It'll stay like that for at least a week.
Head out across the sea in
that direction. Take your time.
You should reach the
island in about four days.
It's going to be a little on the chilly
side, so be sure to bundle up and stay warm.
Is this a dream?
The sea has become as hard as the ground.
We can finally cross it.
Now we'll be able to
get off of this island.
Thank you!
Thanks so much!
It's a miracle!
The Marine granted us a miracle!
All right, then.
Time for us to get going.
Right.
I'm really happy for you guys. Take care.
I guess there are all sorts
of different pirates, huh?
How can we ever thank you for
everything that you've done for us?
Not only did you treat
our sick and injured,
but you shared your food
and water with us as well.
Aw, don't worry about it.
Good things happen to good people.
Just let fate take its course.
Make sure the children don't catch cold.
Keep them bundled up tight.
At any rate, these colder temperatures
should keep your food fresh longer.
Thank you all very much.
We will never forget your kindness.
Take care, Straw Hat pirates! Bye!
Take care, boys!
Be careful on your trip!
Safe journeys to pies!
That felt really good.
It feels like winter just happened.
Check it out! I can skate!
Awesome, jumper!
Man, it's cold. I'm freezing.
What is it?
How should I put this?
You're the spitting image of
your grandfather, Monkey D.
Luffy.
Or maybe I should say you're just
as reckless and hard to figure out.
You knew my grandpa?
Seriously? Luffy's?
Hey, Luffy, what's wrong?
You're sweating.
Uh, nothing.
Really, I'm fine.
Your grandfather helped me
out once, a long time ago.
That's why I'm here.
I wanted to see you and Nico
Robin together with my own eyes.
On second thought, maybe
I should just kill you.
The government still doesn't
consider you a threat,
but I know enough of your history
to see you're a formidable crew.
You may be few in number, but with
the shrewd rogues gathered here,
this crew will likely
be a problem later on.
Considering the circumstances
regarding your initial bounty,
the numerous daring actions you've taken,
and the speed of your overall progress.
I've fought outlaws for most of my life,
but thinking about how you'll turn
out scares the hell out of me.
Hey, wait, hold on a second!
You said you were here to check
things out, not to kill anyone!
One among you I consider
the most dangerous.
That would be you, Nico Robin.
So despite everything,
you are here for Robin.
Now I'm really gonna kick your ass!
The size of her bounty isn't merely a
reflection of her strength and power.
It also represents something else.
That would be the level of threat and danger
that she poses to the world government.
That's why a 79 million
Barry bounty was placed
on her head at the tender
young age of eight.
I'm impressed you were able to
survive, especially as a child.
You managed to betray, sidestep, and
escape from everyone in your past.
and then found a new
partner to make you some.
You survived in the underworld
by being quick to switch sides.
And now you've chosen this
crew as your next haven.
That's enough, jerk!
I'm not just gonna stand here and
let you speak to a lady like that.
What kind of ridiculous grudge
are you holding against Robin?
Stop it, Sanji!
I don't have anything against her.
The only connection we have between us is
that I let her escape from me one time?
but that's about it.
It was a long time ago.
You will all learn soon
enough that protecting
this troublesome woman
leads to nothing but regret.
If you need proof, consider this.
Every organization that
she's had something
to do with in the past
has been annihilated.
Not one single solitary
member escaped except for her.
Why is that, Nico Robin?
Shut up, you jerk!
The past doesn't matter!
I see.
So these poor fools don't suspect a thing.
Just get to the point!
If you want to arrest me, then
why not just do it already?
Prince of Lure!
No!
Robin!
My, my, my Did something
I say strike a nerve?
That's too bad.
I must have overestimated how
reasonable a woman you were.
And clutch.
He shattered it to a million pieces.
It didn't work. We're screwed.
Let's get out of here, everybody.
Run for your lives.
Now, now.
That wasn't a very nice thing to do.
Ice Sabre, I didn't want to
have to kill you, but now.
Slice shoot!
Come go!
Crystal!
He's cool!
He froze up!
He got all three of them at once!
He's freezing them solid.
I have to help quickly.
If they get frostbite, their
lips will start to rot.
Ossum, what are you doing?
We have to save them now. I want to help.
I'm trying to, but I can't see them both.
Did he freeze me too?
No, you're just too scared
to move, coward. Ah! Louis!
Sanzidoro, hold on.
We'll save you.
Robin, run away. Hey!
You have some very loyal friends, but
you will never change, Nico Robin.
No, that's not true!
That's Robin!
Get away from him!
Watch out!
I'm not human.
Robin!
Oh, my God.
You bastard!
Stop yelling.
If you thaw her out
carefully, she'll live.
Her body is extremely fragile in this state,
so you'll need to handle her with care.
If any part of her breaks, she'll die.
For example, if I were to
smash her apart like this...
Noooooooooo!
Nooooooooooooooo! stop it!
Uh?
That was close!
What in the hell are you doing?
Usopp, chumper, quick!
Take Robin and run back to the ship!
Throw her out and keep her safe!
Right, you got it, Captain!
Hurry, be gentle, okay?
It's cold!
I know, but Robin's even colder, genius!
Don't bother.
The world would be a much better
place without that woman in.
Not to split hair.
But a pirate crew pretty much
consists of people just like that.
You got that right, lady.
Now, if you don't mind, kindly step aside.
Nani!
You're not gonna mess
with this crew! Wait!
Nobody attack him!
Stay back and don't interfere.
I'm gonna fight him one-on-one.
What do you say?
The two of us can settle this on our own.
Fine by me.
But since I don't have a ship to take you
back, then I'll just have to kill you.
She can't breathe like this, can she?
I think she's in a state
of suspended animation.
Doesn't that mean she'll die
if we don't do something?
If we warm her up too
quickly, she'll shatter.
We have to restore her body
temperature from the inside out.
Are you sure that this
is really going to work?
I don't know, but it's the only thing I...
Whoa, wait a minute.
You don't know?
This is Robin's life
we're talking about here.
I know, but I've never treated someone
whose entire body was frozen before.
I know that Alkeji said
she was still alive,
but I just don't see how
that could be possible.
Don't give me that crap.
If you can't do anything to save her,
then no one in the whole world can.
You understand me?
You are the doctor of the
Straw Hat pirates, got it?
I know, okay?
Just shut up and stop yelling at me!
Chopper!
What's going on?
Why are just the three of you here?
Where's Luffy?
There's no time to explain.
We need to go back right away.
Help us do something about
this frozen arm and leg.
Oh, right.
We need to douse every part of
your body that's frozen in water.
But we're using the shower room
for Robin. How is Robin? Is she OK?
Uh, it's too early to tell.
What are you doing?
Will this do chop her?
Yes.
Once the ice begins to melt,
start rubbing the affected areas,
and then come up to the ship right away.
Nami, come aboard and help
us treat Robin. Right.
What the?
Why are you guys here?
What happened? Where's Luffy?
Fighting out Cage one-on-one.
One-on-one?
You mean you left Luffy there
to face him all by himself?
Those were the captain's orders.
Are you crazy?
Can't you tell what an
order is unreasonable?
I can't believe you would be so cold-hearted
that I should just leave it there!
It was a duel, can't you understand that?
It's what he wanted!
Stop it, both of you, this isn't the time!
Right now, we need to stay focused, okay?
Whether this decision was one of his
passing whims or not, it doesn't matter.
Whatever happens, we have to be
ready to deal with it, understand?
You really are an odd one, aren't you?
Now it's ice time.
what do you say the two of us can
settle this on our own oh man you
tricked me the moment i agreed to
fight you one-on-one i settled on
defeating you and you alone but that
was your plan wasn't it if i were
to attack your crew now i'd be the
bad guy here isn't that right captain
them.
Or maybe you actually
thought you could beat me.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Keep a close eye on Nico Robin.
Eventually, she'll grow to
be more than you can handle.
The nature of the violent
fate she was born into.
Will be a greater danger
than you can imagine!
More of a burden than you
could ever hope to bear.
That's what it means to have
that woman as part of your crew.
You have been warned.
Mr. Monkey D.
Luffy
It would be easy to break you
and kill you right here and now,
but I have a debt to honor.
Consider us even for you taking
care of crocodile, as well as...
Uh, uh, well, never mind.
Something to do with Smoker?
See ya.
There he is!
Luffy!
He's still in one piece.
That's good news.
I'll carry him, let's get him to the ship!
Stop saying what I'm saying!
If they follow their Log Pose from
this island, their next destination is
It's Water 7, the city of water huh?
oh my my my?
would you look at that?
They're getting really close to
our headquarters, aren't they?
Both of their hearts are beating!
Yeah!
Sophie!
You can't go in yet!
I don't want them disturbed, understand?
Hey, Dr.
Chopper, how about I make them some food?
Calling me doctor won't make me feel
happy or anything, you stupid jerk.
But I suppose some warm drinks
would be nice for when they wake up.
I'll carry them into the lounge later.
Aye, aye, sir!
Hey, Nami, should we set sail?
No, not yet.
Not while the captain's out of commission.
The lock pose has our new heading,
but let's rest here for the day.
What's wrong, your son?
You look beat.
Are there going to be more guys like him?
Coming after us everywhere we go?
This is crazy.
I don't know how much
more of it I can take.
Get some sleep, idiot.
You're just exhausted, okay?
Thank you.